Guide to the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Communications Department records, 1958-1983 IBT0005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Newspaper Clippings, ibt0005 Series 2; This series consists of copies of newspaper articles drawn from local newspaper in the U.S. and Canada, 1996-2003. The clippings are organized by date and the set of clippings for each date is indexed and the IBT locals that they deal with are highlighted on 
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 February; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 February; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 March; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 March; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 March; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 April; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 April; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 May; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 June; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 June; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 July; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 July; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 August; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1998 September; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1998 October; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1998 November; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1998 December; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 Janruary; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 February; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 March; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 March; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 May; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 June; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 July; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 August; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 September; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 November; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 November; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1999 December; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 Janruary; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 February; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 February; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 March; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 March; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 March; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 April; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 April; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 April; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 May; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 May; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 May; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 May; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 June; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 June; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 June; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 June; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 June; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 July; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 July; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 July; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 July; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 August; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 August; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 August; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 August; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 September; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 September; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 September; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 September; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 September; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 September; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 October; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 October; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 October (Box 28, Binder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 November; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 November; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 November; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 November; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 November; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 November; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 November; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 December; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 December; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 December; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2000 December (Box 29, Binder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 January; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 January; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 January; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 January; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 Janruary; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 Janruary; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 February; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 February; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 February; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 February; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 February; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 March; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 March; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 March; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 March; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 March; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 April; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 April; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 April; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 April; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 May (Box 29, Binder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 June; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 June; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 June; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 June; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 July; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 July; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 July; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 August; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 August; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 August; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 August; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 September; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 September; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 September; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 September; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 September; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 September; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 September; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 October; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 October; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 October; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 October; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 October; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 October; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 November; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 November; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 November; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 November; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 November; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 November; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 November; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 December; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 December; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 December; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 December; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2001 December; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 January; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 February; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 February; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 February; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 February; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 February; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 February; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 March; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 April; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 May; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 May; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 May; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 May; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 May; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 May 29 - 2002 June 03; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 June; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 June; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 June; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 June; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 June; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 June; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 July; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 July; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 July; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 July; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 July 30 - 2002 August 1; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 August; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 August; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 August; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 August; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 August; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 September; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 September; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 September; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 September; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 September; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 October; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 October; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 October (Box 24, Binder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 October (Box 24, Binder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2002 November 19 - 2002 December 26 (Box 24, Binder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 January (Box 25, Binder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 February (Box 25, Binder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 February (Box 25, Binder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 March 27 - 2003 April 21 (Box 26, Binder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 April 22 - 2003 May 13 (Box 26, Binder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 May 14 - 2003 June 17 (Box 26, Binder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 June 18 - 2003 July 16 (Box 27, Binder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 July 21 - 2003 August 18 (Box 27, Binder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 August 20 - 2003 September 17 (Box 27, Binder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 2003 September 22 - 2003 October 20 (Box 28, Binder 1)
  - "The Facts Behind 'F.I.S.T.'", Steven Brill, May 23, 1978; Series 2 (Box 30, Folder 7)